<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Sailing On Dreams - Playing mind games with soul]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Sailing On Dreams - Playing mind games with soul]]></description>
        <link>http://www.sailingondreams.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 21:07:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.sailingondreams.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Face]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Face</h1><p>It’s not every day that you find yourself screaming at a stranger in the middle of a bridge. She just hit me full on with her car while I was trying to cross. The sandwich shop a bit ahead seemed interesting, and I had priority. The impact dislocated my left knee. It clicked back, meaning I am standing on a painful leg.“What the hell were you doing?” I ask severely agitated. “I had priority”“I had to brake! You were not paying attention!” she calls back. “You should have seen that I was driving here”“I saw you. I was just looking at that sandwich shop, because it seems that they have good sandwiches. You had no right to drive on. I had priority. If I’d walked thirty-three centimeters further, you’d have killed me!” This last part is bluff. I want to add some spice to the moment. I think it’s a suitable way to express my vulnerability as a pedestrian.“Thirty three centimeters? Not 32 or 34?” she asks mockingly.“That is not the point. The point is that you made a big mistake by entering my knee. I’m going to sue you.” To add some power to my words, I point my finger straight at her not unpleasant face. I take a step in her direction with my painful leg. She remains terribly calm.“You were not paying attention to the road, drama queen. Your mind was on sandwiches. Besides, you were walking too fast.”“If I was walking quickly, that was because of the appealing way in which they presented the sandwiches in that shop. I cannot help that. Just look at it.”“Well, that’s right, but I’m not filling in the papers with you, and I’m certainly not letting you sue me.”“You have no say in that!” I roar. “I’ll note down your licence plate number and go to the police.”I stumble to the back of her car. This should shut her up.“You know what, mister tall man, why don’t you go for a swim?” She grabs me by the chest, and tips my good leg out of balance. Backwards, I hobble and bobble over the street while she insists on bringing me to the fence. I realise this is not going the way I want it to when my bottom hits it. When she grabs my inner thighs, I’m shocked, when she pulls them up: astonished. That felt good for a second. Now, my centre of gravity is on a side of the fence where it should not.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/141db995-34eb-4fe1-9113-e98bf2ada2e4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.sailingondreams.com/face/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7054c03b-52eb-415e-9a97-22d588f227e7</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 21:07:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Couch at Sunset]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Couch at Sunset</h1><p>The doorbell makes me jump. I should lower the volume one day. One of those things I keep postponing. Standing up as slowly as I can helps me tame the excitement this bell forces upon me. It’s something I’m vaguely aware of. In the meantime, my steps show that somebody just made me rise out of my very comfortable chair. Well… as long as Ifeel in command… I open the door. It’s a girl. A woman. She is standing thirty-three centimetres from the threshold. She has natural red hair. Green eyes. Some freckles accentuate her cheeks. Pointy chin, elegant jaws. Fragile neck, I’m quite sure I could break it. A little hole between her collarbones. Her waist, her legs, her breasts. Oh, her breasts. I recognize her.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.sailingondreams.com/couch-at-sunset/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a6541a2e-798e-48e2-b5c9-87e18b267213</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 21:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>I have to slow down to blow my nose. The napkin bill is going through the roof. It’s the time of the year. I’m on a two-hour drive to the sea-shore because I had to get out. The house is too small sometimes, the city too loud. My mind clogs together with the decor of my days.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.sailingondreams.com/i-have-to-slow-down-to-blow-my-nose-the-napkin-bill-is-goin/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">97f4fecf-47bf-4709-a63b-5f49abd627b7</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 20:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>